<resources>
    <!--app data-->
    <string name="app_name">Github Manual</string>
    <string name="githubDef">\tGitHub is a code hosting platform for version control and collaboration. It lets you and others work together on projects from anywhere.</string>

    <!--Version control relate data (first button)-->
    <string name="btn_1">Version Control?</string>
    <string name="VCSDef">\t\tIn software engineering, version control is a class of systems responsible for managing changes to computer programs, documents, large web sites, or other collections of information. Version control is a component of software configuration management.</string>
    <string name="VCS_Frag">What is Version Control</string>


    <!--Repositry related data (second button)-->
    <string name="btn_2">Repository?</string>
    <string name="REP_Def">A location for storage, often for safety or preservation. (computing) a storage location for files, such as downloadable software packages, or files in a source control system. A burial vault. (figuratively) A person to whom a secret is entrusted.</string>
    <string name="REP_Frag">What is Repository</string>


    <!--Commit Related data (3rd button)-->
    <string name="btn_3">Commit?</string>
    <string name="COM_Def">In version control systems, a commit is an operation which sends the latest changes of the source code to the repository, making these changes part of the head revision of the repository. Unlike commits in data management, commits in version control systems are kept in the repository indefinitely.</string>
    <string name="COM_Frag">What is Commit</string>


    <!--Branch Related Data (4th button)-->
    <string name="btn_4">Branch?</string>
    <string name="BRN_Frag">What is Branch</string>
    <string name="BRN_Def">A branch represents an independent line of development. Branches serve as an abstraction for the edit/stage/commit process. You can think of them as a way to request a brand new working directory, staging area, and project history.</string>

    <string name="btn_x">Github Docs</string>
    <string name="gitDocs">https://docs.github.com/en</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

</resources>